Warm up a little bit, you had or not?
Nah, I feel good in here. I say that.
How was practice?
Chilly.
Might be a little bit. It's going to be
a little chilly in
I'm hearing.
That's what I'm hearing.
Does that change how you approach a game
at all?
No, not really. I mean, I can't do
nothing.
What's the coldest you've ever played?
New England.
Oh, yeah.
Too cold.
By the time you get warmed up and and
kick off, is are you warmed up literally
or are you still cold and you got to
stay by the heater as much as possible?
>> Um
I usually just try to get my hands and
feet warm as possible. That's the
That's the money makers. I got to make
sure I'm moving around on those and make
sure they're ready to ready for the ball
or anything. How do you feel like the
Bills game went for you personally?
Um
It was pretty boring, if I'll be honest,
but
love seeing T go crazy at the end of the
day. You know, I'm all a team player.
Um so, I mean
I can't complain about that. Was it more
of what Was it just I think Ben
Roethlisberger followed you throughout
the game? Was it more just getting
doubled or what was that kind of a Uh
it's just
It is really just hard to run real like
real routes in the snow out there, you
know what I'm saying? Um especially
trying to beat the leverages that they
was giving me.
Um
you know, when we did have opportunities
where we did we didn't click on them.
So, you know, it was just just one of
them opportunities. Joe said after the
game that, you know, they made it a
point to take you away. Do you feel like
after what happened against Baltimore
the first time that you might see a
different coverage look than you saw in
the first game against them?
Uh I'm sure they might do similar
things. They might do the same thing but
make it look different, but I'm sure
they they're going to do some similar
things and just add on.
When T made Well, which catch did you
think was more impressive? Was Ja'Marr
Chase's catch?
Obviously, the first one was one we
needed, but the one hand was
insane. Yeah. Yeah.
Great catch. Have you talked to him this
week about, you know, coming back and
playing and kind of what's the
conversation been between the two of
y'all as he gets ready?
Um no, we don't really Um we don't
really talking about like what he going
to do for the game. I'm just talking to
him regular like what we do every day.
Um being social, being friends, you know
what I'm saying? Just taking his mind
away from, you know, the stuff that he's
going through and just letting him be
himself for a minute. Are you concerned
at all about kind of his health moving
forward? Kind of he's taking some hard
hits these last couple weeks. I mean,
what's what's that like as a guy who's
friends with him? He's tied to the hip
with him. What's that like seeing him
kind of go through this?
Um
I I would say I'm always concerned with
his health. I feel like the same with
y'all. I feel like anybody on the team,
especially people that I'm real close
with. Um but at the end of the day
I always tell I always tell them like,
you know, we got to do what we could do
for our body at the end of the day.
That's going to make us better.
Um
Whatever he got going on, you know, I
don't really tell him what to do at the
end of the day. I'm just being there and
being positive for him. When you have to
go up and you're you're trying to make a
contested catch and you're high pointing
the ball and stuff like T has and then
he lands on his head. Is there anything
as a receiver you can do
Your uh your hands are obviously out
here trying to catch the ball, so
what can you do to avoid hitting your
head like that? Um
Is there anything?
I mean, yeah, but in a moment it's hard
to say, you know what I'm saying? Cuz in
a moment it's not
And sometimes you don't really have that
much control over your body as you
falling, you know what I'm saying? You
might step on on his foot or something
and uh your whole body movement change.
So, it's it's really hard to say when
it's in the moment. After the game, he's
talked about being a soldier and you
know, you guys are soldiers.
It's the name of the game. You take
hits. You get back up. You try to play.
What is the fine line? Have you ever
faced that moment tomorrow where
you know, I want to keep playing, but
I'm like you just said, want to do
what's going to take care of my body at
the same It seems like a fine line to
walk.
Um I mean, yeah, it's a fine line to
walk, but it's everybody going to have
their opinion on it at the end of the
day, but um
it's you got to think about yourself at
the end of the day putting yourself out
there.
Your career, your life, your line, you
know what I'm saying? So, your
generation, your legacy is all on the
line, whatever you do. So, that's all it
How much How much do you and T, Joe,
whoever it is, Chase Brown
How much do you guys talk about that?
We don't really talk about that so much,
you know what I'm saying? At the end of
the day, um
we we always in the building. All we
talk about is football majority of the
time. We trying to find stuff to do
that's not football. Trying to find
hobbies, trying to hang out, go eat and
stuff like that.
How much time do you spend with
like
you know, with like
your other offensive captains like
Orlando who's, you know,
been a captain for a couple of years.
You know, what's your view of him and do
you pick his brain at all on
being a
captain or anything? Um
A lot of positivity from Orlando and
just positive energy from Orlando.
Um
He's one of the guys, you know, before
last year, you know, I would talk to him
a lot. He would talk to me a lot. We
would always have conversations still to
this day where me and him always just
just constantly talking about anything,
little things like you saying. So, we
talked about it all.
He He seems to be kind of a natural
I
you know, you talk
you know, I think pretty eloquently
about how
you you've had
look at the role
>> Mhm. growing into it and everything like
that and he seems kind of like this kind
of like a natural
guy. Yeah, yeah.
Yeah, it's definitely got to be his
character at the end of the day. You
know what I'm saying? He walks in and
he's the same person every day. Never
seen him one day he's been
annoyed, mad, or sad you know, about,
you know, what he comes in and doing in
his personal life. He comes in every day
the same person.
Does a guy like that have an impact on
the locker room?
Yes. I would say so, yes.
What What do you feel like y'all's
biggest objective is over the next four
games? Say it again? What do you What do
you feel like y'all's biggest objective
should be over the next four games? Um
finish strong.
And of course, we got to win out, but we
just got to finish strong. That's the
best thing.
One game at a time.
How much How much do you think Joe
Burrow loves football?
Um
I thought this was a AI.
I'm not This This really happened,
though? They That's real
>> Yeah.
Well, it depends on what you saw. I
don't really know nothing about it at
the end of the day, you know what I'm
saying? That's something
>> You might have seen something that we're
not.
>> I mean, but like I've seen a little bit
from the TV walking outside from
practice and then like I turned my eyes,
but I don't know nothing about it. At
the end of the day, I
I see him the same every day. To me, he
loves football.
You know what I'm saying? But that's a
him question. I can't answer that for
him. You know what I'm saying at the end
of the day?
>> asking for your perspective. I'm not
trying to I don't know. From what I see,
I see the same person every day. You
know, he comes to work. He loves work.
You know what I'm saying? So, I mean he
don't look like he's bummed to be here,
you know?
But
>> same every day.
I think when after the Baltimore game,
you know, you asked us like, did you
think he was emotional cuz we asked you.
Uh you know, it seems like this is kind
of really hit him a little bit
differently than all the other times.
Now, after seeing him for the last few
weeks, what do you think?
Hm. Y'all know y'all be really putting
Y'all be putting some clues together,
boy. I swear.
Um
Honestly,
nothing's wrong with a little emotion at
the end of the day, especially coming
back from injury.
The man The man loves the game. I think
he loves the game from what I what I've
learned from him also at the end of the
day, you know what I'm saying? So,
um
I can't really say what he feels at the
end of the day, but from what I see,
man, he seems the same every day.
Comes to work ready to play. Comes to
practice the same guy. He's
helps me every day. You know, it's it's
no negativity in the building from him,
so.
What was his reaction to you guys
singing Happy Birthday yesterday?
He don't like it, so I think
I don't know whose idea it was. I was
trying to get a cake brought in here to
piss him off a little bit more cuz I
know he don't really do that.
So, I just wanted to show him like, bro,
we appreciate you, bro. Let's get a big
cake for you and, you know, I wanted to
give him a little kick in the face, but
It's good seeing him like that, you know
what I'm saying? I know he don't like
it, but
I like seeing him like that sometimes.
He need to embrace it. Have you ever
gotten him anything for his birthday
over the years? Y'all have known each
other for a while now. Nah.
I might do something for Christmas. Who
knows?
What do you What What do you When Joe is
like at his enjoying everything the
most? When do you When is Joe is ever at
his happiest? You You've played with him
for so many years. When is he in his
like his best mood?
Um I can't tell.
I can't tell.
If I'll be honest,
like he smiles every day. Like
like
the narrative that y'all are trying to
paint on him right now, I don't see it.
You know what I'm saying at the end of
the day? He's the same person every day.
He comes to work. He loves work.
He loves the guys in the locker room, so
he's pretty positive to me. There's no
narrative. We're just asking questions.
Just let the for the mic.
>> bit of narrative. It's okay.
How I hate the How
What do you think Joe would be like if
he wasn't a quarterback? And he wasn't
playing.
Right now at this age. What would he be
doing?
I would probably say he'd be doing
something like NASA. He'd be doing
something with NASA or he'd be messing
with like uh sculptures or something
like that. Sculptures? Yeah, like old
bones.
Like dinosaur bones. Like He'd be doing
something like that.
There you go. Sorry. Is it okay to ask a
football Sure. Go ahead.
Whatever. For Joe's.
I made a newspaper not psychotic.
Um
Was just wondering about this secondary,
you know, Hamilton's getting a lot of
Hamilton's getting a lot of play,
especially, you know, last month or so.
I'm wondering if uh cuz I know you had
said going into that game
maybe he's covered twice or something.
Did Did you see him at all and uh the
way they're using him? Is it different
than in the past?
What do you think of him as a player?
Um
He is a good player overall. Um
I we I haven't checked him or he hasn't
checked me last game or nothing like
that. He just like lined up over me.
Um
And you know they they they they have
been using him I could say differently
cuz
last time we played like you said he
checked me on one of the one of the
routes and the previous year before that
so um who knows you know what I'm saying
as they they probably all use him a
little different.
Do they Does that make it
you know? What do you think of the back
end there? What do you think of them as
a whole back and how they play? Veteran
group.
Um honestly I love playing Baltimore. At
the end of the day those those guys
all those DBs are good work at the end
of the day. Um from the nickel spot to
outside from safety everybody is a good
good competition across the board and
just getting good work during the game.
You and Cheeto go way back and I guess
just
just like training camp huh? Yeah that's
my guy right there. Yeah. I like Cheeto.
You guys talk during the game?
We actually don't. We've been through
hell and at practice so me and him we
actually didn't say a word to each
other.
Maybe like three words or something like
that. Is that a Is that a sign of
respect kind of for what you have for
him? Yeah out of respect.
I don't really talk trash to Cheeto you
know what I'm saying? What was your
reaction when he signed with Baltimore
initially?
Um
I get another opportunity against him
you know what I'm saying? That's how I
look at it at the end of the day. I like
Cheeto. So I like going against him you
know what I'm saying? When he returned I
like Cheeto when he was released by the
Titans. Yeah yeah yeah. Yeah. You know
what I'm saying? And he helped me when I
was a rookie too so like it it goes back
all the way back for me getting reps
with him so
just showing how far I came and you know
just putting the skill against skill. So
you guys had your rookie narratives
right?
Say it again? The rookie narratives
during training camp were finally It's a
lie y'all y'all y'all paint a picture
for everybody you know what I'm saying?
It happens. And another football
question.
Do you prefer catching the ball on the
run
or
sitting in a zone and making somebody
miss and then making a big play?
And why?
Um
Well I would I would love to say
catching run cuz it's a little easier
being a little bit be more in stride and
you know what I'm saying? Just be faster
run past people but
it all depends on the coverage at the
end of the day you know? So I would pick
the first one. Would you say at this
point in your career you you feel
you feel like you do both equally well?
Yes. I would say I'm well-rounded.
When you say Cheeto helped you you mean
on the field being such a good DB or
were there conversations? Was there a
big brother element?
Um so both you know what I'm saying? At
the end of the day both. Um
me learning the technique me asking
questions
him telling me what he see from me you
know what I'm saying? And you know me
and him kicked it up from out the
facility a couple times too so you
overall he a good good person good
overall dude. How important looking back
was it to have good veterans in that 21
group as y'all were kind of
transitioning to have to kind of show
some of the young guys the ropes on
whatever side of the ball it was? How
important was that to y'all's success
over the years in 21 and 22?
Um that was that was great DBs man if
I'm being honest. Um I learned a lot
from those guys. Um that whole year I
learned a lot period you know what I'm
saying from those guys so
like I said they helped me along this
journey too you know what I'm saying?
Every one of those guys. Speaking of DBs
what's the evolution of DJ Turner and
Mike and seeing him
thrive and be as sticky in coverage as
he's been this season? Yeah. Um
so we had good reps in in camp if I'm
being honest. We had a really good reps
in camp and
um
I think that's when I knew you know he
was going to be
having a great year at the end of the
time.
And um
it really just happened out of nowhere
if I'm being honest you know and
when the games came it just he just made
more and more plays and just look easy
to him. What's unique about him as a as
a corner? What what
stands out the most when you're going
against him without
giving away the secret sauce I guess.
Uh I would say
you know I would say he's he's versatile
corner at the end of the day like you
know
he's not afraid to switch it up his
techniques.
You guys have some you guys have some
really good games.
201 game in your rookie year
some others. Um is it you know and
they're and they're good. I mean is that
kind of bring out the best in you when
you're
going against guys that you know so
well?
Um
I want to say that a lot of the time
they they
I don't I wouldn't say that.
You know what I'm saying? I
I play the I feel like I play
the best against everybody. At the end
of the day I feel like I go out there
and play my hardest against everybody
but you know some games just so happen
to be better than other games at the end
of the day. Just so happen to be it
don't matter who I play against.
Thanks Rashod. Rashod you got Rashod.
Thanks. That was like 20 minutes today
huh? Some good newspaper questions
Emily.